Ben: It’s a beautiful evening.
Izzy: Yes, it is. I love it here.
I came here a lot with my dad when I was a child.
Ben: Did you live near here?
Izzy: Not far. We lived in Camden Town.
Ben: Oh, nice.
Izzy: So…do you really want to see my photos now?
Ben: Yes, I do.
Izzy: Here. Go ahead. This is my portfolio.
Ben: Wow, these are…really professional.
Amazing, Izzy!
Izzy: Thanks…You know, there’s this job I really want…well, I think I want it…
Ben: What job?
Izzy: I want to be a photo editor.
I…sent in an application and I got an interview.
Ben: Wow, that’s great!
Izzy: But…I don’t know.
Ben: You don’t know, what?
Izzy: Well…I’ve never worked in a job like that before.
I’m not sure I’m ready for it.
Ben: Izzy. Your photos are awesome!
I think the magazine would be lucky to have you.
Izzy: Do you think so?
Ben: Yeah! Of course!
Izzy: I think so, too.
You can say more nice things about my photos now.
Ben: Ah, yes, ma’am. Ah, wow, look at this one.
Now that is amazing! And that one? Incredible!
That, now that is just wonderful.
Perfection, perfection.
Izzy: Thank you, Ben.